// Questions Object

var qObj = [{
    question:"What year was the U.S. Marine Corps Established?",
    options: ["1801","1871","1775","1790"],
    answer: "2"
},{
    question:"Where was the U.S. Marine Corps started?",
    options: ["Philadelphia","Washington DC","New York","England"],
    answer: "0"
},{
    question:"What is the U.S. Marine Corps Motto ?",
    options: ["Kill or be Killed","Semper Fidelis","Carpe Diem","Get Some!"],
    answer: "1"
},{
    question:"What is the mascot for the U.S. Marine Corps?",
    options: ["Bald Eagle","Beagle","Great Dane","English Bull Dog"],
    answer: "3"
},{
    question:"The U.S. Marine Corps Reserve operates which non-profit organization?",
    options: ["Toys for Tots","Cancer Figthers of US","Retired Vets of US","Animal protectures of USA"],
    answer: "0"
},{
    question:"What reading list is published every year for U.S. Marines?",
    options: ["Oprah's book Club","Commandant's Professional Reading List","Commanders Annual Reading List","Reading for Marines"],
    answer: "1"
},{
    question:"Who was the 13th Commandant of the Marine Corps?",
    options: ["Samuel Nicholas","George Barnett","John A. Lejeune","Michael Hagee"],
    answer: "2"
},{
    question:"What is the name of the Marine Corps mascot?",
    options: ["Jarhead","Oscar","Sam","Chesty"],
    answer: "3"
},{
    question:"Where to female Marines attend Bootcamp?",
    options: ["MCRD Parris Island","MCRD San Diego","Camp Lejeune","Ft Jackson"],
    answer: "0"
},{
    question:"Who was the 1st Commandant of the Marine Corps?",
    options: ["Samuel Nicholas","George Barnett","John A. Lejeune","Michael Hagee"],
    answer: "0"
}
];
